Guide to the Stanford Oral History Project Interviews SC1017
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Silicon Valley Project Interviews, Series 6 (Box 5)
  - Linvill, John, 1919-2011, 1987 May 5; 243; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
    Electrical Engineering (Stanford Center for Integrated Systems). Integrated electronics. Developed the Optacon (electronic reading device for the blind). Telesensory Systems; Spectra Physics, Cromemco, Anderson-Jacobson.
    - Transcript (Box 9)
  - Nunan, Craig, 1989 Jan 12, 13, 17; 266_269; 4 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
    - Transcript (Box 9)
  - Packard, Martin, 1988 May-Jul, Oct; 244_251; 8 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
    Received his Ph.D. in physics from Stanford in 1949, under Professor Felix Bloch. Developed the technique of nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR) and applied it to chemistry and other fields. Varian Associates, 1951 to present (Vice President since 1963, Assistant to the Chairman since 1974).
    - Transcript (Box 9)
- Dr. Robert Reid Newell Interviews, Series 7 (Box 6)
  - Abrams, Herbert L., 1990 Apr 25; 275; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Beard, Rodney, 1986 May 21; 303; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Transcript (Box 9)
  - Jones, Henry, 1987 Apr 16; 301; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Transcript (Box 9)
  - Kriss, Joseph P., 1919-1989, 1986 Jul 1; 276, 302; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
  - Lowenstein, Gerald, 1988 Mar 21; 304; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
  - Newell, Alan, 1986 Jun 26; 296_298; 3 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Transcript (Box 9)
  - Newell, Jeanette, 1986 Apr 7; 299_300; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
  - Richards, Victor, 1989 Feb 1; 277; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
- Administrative Files
  Conditions Governing Access
  Files are restricted for 50 yeards from date of creation.
  - SOHP Administrative files: General (Box 34)
  - SOHP Administrative files: Fund-Raising, Finances and Gifts (Box 35)
  - SOHP Administrative files: General Oral History Info and Resources (Box 35)
  - SOHP Administrative files: How To (oral history techniques, computers) (Box 35)
  - SOHP Administrative files: Models, Forms and Procedures (Box 35)
  - SOHP Administrative files: Personnel and Volunteer Records (Box 36)
  - SOHP Administrative files: Potential Oral History Projects (Box 37)
  - SOHP Administrative files: Oral History Assoc. materials (Box 38)